<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LagosTourGuide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Lagos Tour</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">adewalekayode90@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text">Experience the beauty of Lagos</string>


    <!--Religious Places Pioneer/ presidents strings-->
    <string name="president_religion_1">President; Rev (Dr) Chris Oyakhilome, This is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="president_religion_2">General Overseer: Pastor EA AdeboyeThis is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="president_religion_3"> General Overseer: Pastor WF KumuyiThis is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="president_religion_4">Senior Pastor; Pastor Sam AdeyemiThis is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="president_religion_5">Senior Pastor; Pastor Poju OyemadeThis is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria </string>
    <string name="president_religion_6">Founder: Bishop David Oyedepo This is one of the
        biggest churches in Nigeria, with its headquarter in Lagos Nigeria</string>

    <!--Religious Places strings-->
    <string name="religion_1">Christ Embassy Church</string>
    <string name="religion_2">Reedemed Church</string>
    <string name="religion_3">Deeper life</string>
    <string name="religion_4">Daystar</string>
    <string name="religion_5">Covenant Christtan Centre </string>
    <string name="religion_6">Winner Chapel</string>


    <!--Tourist attractions strings-->
    <string name="tourist_1">National Theatre</string>
    <string name="tourist_2">Nigerian National Museum</string>
    <string name="tourist_3">The New Afrika Shrine</string>
    <string name="tourist_4">Hi Impact Planet</string>
    <string name="tourist_5">Lekki Conservation Centre </string>
    <string name="tourist_6">Tarkwa Bay Beach</string>
    <string name="tourist_7">Lekki Leisure Lake</string>
    <string name="tourist_8">Terra Kulture </string>
    <string name="tourist_9">Elegushi Beach</string>


    <!--Tourist attractions descriptions strings-->
    <string name="desc_tourist_1">An architectural masterpiece and cultural landmark,
        the edifice is one of the few properties of the country
        that has stood the test of time. Being home to everything art,
        the National Theatre provides an avenue for you to learn a lot more
        about art while having fun in its lush environment.</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_2">Representing a country overflowing with diverse cultural heritage,
        the Nigerian national museum is the perfect expo of Nigerian history.
        Showcasing works of art dating back to the pre-independence era,
        the museum tells the story of Nigeria’s journey through
        years of progressive growth.</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_3">The New Afrika Shrine is an open-air
        entertainment centre located in Ikeja, Lagos State.
        It serves as the host location of the annual Felabration music festival.
        Currently managed by Femi Kuti and Yeni Anikulapo-Kuti,
        it is the replacement of the old Afrika Shrine created in 1970 by Fela Kuti until
        it was burnt down in 1977.</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_4">Hi-Impact Planet offers world-class fun for the young and old,
        friends and families. There are games, rides and other entertaining attractions for the
        young and young at heart. </string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_5">This nature hub is run by the Nigerian conservation foundation
        (NCF) and If you appreciate the sight of plants and animals in their natural habitat,
        then this place is a must visit for you. </string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_6">Tarkwa Bay Beach, unlike most public beaches in Lagos,
        isn’t often noisy or overcrowded. This makes it a great place for some alone time with your
        significant other or perhaps a fun day out with your friends.</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_7">At Lekki Leisure Lake you can partake in thrilling
        adventurous activities like quad biking, jet skiing, zip lining and much more!</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_8">The internationally acclaimed art house, Terra Kulture is the
        home of contemporary visual and theatre arts in Nigeria. It stands as one of only 2 art
        auction houses in Nigeria, with a collection of over a thousand art pieces
        from across the country.</string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_9">Elegushi Royal Beach is a private beach owned by the Elegushi
        Royal family, led by HRM Oba Alayeluwa Saheed Ademola Elegushi.
        It is arguably the most popular beaches in Lagos. </string>

    <string name="desc_tourist_10">Located in Lekki, the Oniru Beach is great for public holiday
        visits and weekend leisure. You can swim in the Atlantic Ocean
        and ride horses on the white sand beach.</string>


    <!--Hotels strings-->
    <string name="hotel_1">Sheraton Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_2">Eho Hotel and suites</string>
    <string name="hotel_3">De Reinessance</string>
    <string name="hotel_4">K and G</string>
    <string name="hotel_5">Oriental Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_6">360 Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_7">Air bnb</string>
    <string name="hotel_8">Sarah Sam</string>
    <string name="hotel_9">Ibis Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_10">White house</string>

    <!--Hotels Address strings-->
    <string name="address_hotel_1">Located at; Opebi Road, Ikeja Gra, one of the 5 star hotels in
        Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_2">Located at; Victoria Island, one of the 5 star hotels in
        Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_3">Located at; Alausa, Ikeja, one of the 5 star hotels in
        Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_4">Located at; Oregun, Ikeja, also a nice hotel</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_5">Located at; Lekki, VI, also a nice hotel</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_6">Located at; Lekki, Ajah, also a nice hotel</string>

    <string name="address_hotel_7">Located at; Online, you make your bookings for hotels,
        and any form of accommodation on this platform, although does not have a hotel of its own but
        they are the best in the business</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_8">Located at; Ogudu, Ojota, this is also a nice hote</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_9">Located at; Opebi, Ikeja, this is one of the best hotels
        in Lagos Nigeria, can't forget their morning buffet, for all guests</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_10">Located at; Opebi, ikeja, this is also a nice hotel</string>

    <!--Lagos Festivals strings-->
    <string name="festivals_1">Eyo Festival</string>
    <string name="festivals_2">Lagos Black Heritage festivals</string>
    <string name="festivals_3">Lagos International Jazz Festival </string>
    <string name="festivals_4">Yoruba Arts Festival </string>
    <string name="festivals_5">Eko International Film Festival  </string>
    <string name="festivals_6">Boat Regattas l</string>
    <string name="festivals_7">Lagos Food festival </string>


    <!--Lagos Festivals descriptions strings-->
    <string name="desc_festivals_1">With originsfrom 1750, this festival has masquerades of
        performers in white robes and dancers. The attraction is held in the Tafawa Belewa Square
        and has thousands of attendees each year. </string>

    <string name="desc_festivals_2">The Lagos Black Heritage Festival takes place in April.
        Carnival processions stroll through the street in remembrance of the African slave
        trade story.</string>

    <string name="desc_festivals_3">also known as Lagos Jazz Fest, is an annual celebration of
        the music and culture that takes place in Lagos. Held since 2008, the Lagos International
        Jazz Festival is a three-day event. </string>

    <string name="desc_festivals_4">celebrating the rich, colorful and vibrant Arts and Culture
        of the Yoruba\'s from around the world. Featuring Cultural performances, Workshops,
        Arts and crafts, Competitions, African Market, African food and live music from artists
        and bands dhowcasing the wide variety of popular Yoruba music such as Afrobeats, Juju,
        Highlife, Apala and Jazz. </string>

    <string name="desc_festivals_5">The mission of Eko International Film Festival is to promote
        the appreciation of Arts and Culture through the motion picture arts and sciences and
        increase tourism in Nigeria.  </string>

    <string name="desc_festivals_6">The activities scheduled to spice the cultural festival include,
        performances by entertainment boats, traditional boat regatta parade, cultural display by
        various riverine communities, water safety tips as well as other side attractions. </string>
    <string name="desc_festivals_7">This is an international food and beverage trade fair and events
        that will showcase products from various local and international food and drink
        companies and industries </string>
    <string name="tourist">Tourist</string>
    <string name="religious">Religious</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="fesivals">Fesivals</string>
</resources>
